DAN KLEIN: Now, there are
going to be problems.
So for example, let's take a look at
this case in the Australia graph.
Western Australia has been assigned
red, Queensland has been assigned
green, and we've run our
forward checking.
So at this point, everything
looks good, right?
All unassigned variables still have
legal values in their domain.
For example, in the northern territories
we can still assign blue.
And in southern Australia we
can still assign blue.
Now of course, what would happen
if we actually assigned
blue to both of those?
Well, we'd violate a constraint.
Now, forward checking doesn't
know about this, right?
This is a problem between two unassigned
variables, and forward
checking doesn't deal with that.
But it might be nice if we could know
that the consequences of our decision
further out in the graph somewhere have
already doomed us to failure, so
we can backtrack early.
OK, so let's see if we can come up
with a better approach here.
The general class of methods that reason
from constraint to constraint
are called constraint
propagation methods.
We're going to talk about one particular
constraint propagation
method called enforcing
arc consistency.